<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Activity1</string>
    <string name="view1">NEWS</string>
    <string name="view2">BLOGS</string>
    <string name="view3">ESSAYS</string>
    <string name="button_key">TextView</string>
    <string name="heading1">NEWS</string>
    <string name="heading2">BLOGS</string>
    <string name="heading3">ESSAYS</string>
    <string name="content1">News is information about current events. This may be provided through many different media: word
        of mouth, printing, postal systems, broadcasting, electronic communication, or through the testimony of observers and
        witnesses to events.
        \n\n
        Common topics for news reports include war, government, politics, education, health, the environment, economy,
        business, fashion, and entertainment, as well as athletic events, quirky or unusual events. Government proclamations,
        concerning royal ceremonies, laws, taxes, public health, and criminals, have been dubbed news since ancient times.
        Technological and social developments, often driven by government communication and espionage networks, have increased
        the speed with which news can spread, as well as influenced its content. The genre of news as we know it today is
            closely associated with the newspaper.
        \n\n
        The English word "news" developed in the 14th century as a special use of the plural form of "new". In Middle English,
        the equivalent word was newes, like the French nouvelles and the German Neues. Similar developments are found in
        the Slavic languages – namely the Czech and Slovak noviny (from nový, "new"), the cognate Polish nowiny, the
        Bulgarian novini, and Russian novosti – and in the Celtic languages: the Welsh newyddion (from newydd) and the
            Cornish nowodhow.</string>
    <string name="content2">A blog (a truncation of "weblog")[1] is a discussion or informational website published on the
        World Wide Web consisting of discrete, often informal diary-style text entries (posts). Posts are typically displayed
        in reverse chronological order, so that the most recent post appears first, at the top of the web page. Until 2009,
        blogs were usually the work of a single individual,[citation needed] occasionally of a small group, and often covered
        a single subject or topic. In the 2010s, "multi-author blogs" (MABs) emerged, featuring the writing of multiple
        authors and sometimes professionally edited. MABs from newspapers, other media outlets, universities, think tanks,
        advocacy groups, and similar institutions account for an increasing quantity of blog traffic. The rise of Twitter
        and other microblogging systems helps integrate MABs and single-author blogs into the news media. Blog can also
        be used as a verb, meaning to maintain or add content to a blog.
        \n\n
        The emergence and growth of blogs in the late 1990s coincided with the advent of web publishing tools that
        facilitated the posting of content by non-technical users who did not have much experience with HTML or computer
        programming. Previously, a knowledge of such technologies as HTML and File Transfer Protocol had been required to
        publish content on the Web, and early Web users therefore tended to be hackers and computer enthusiasts. In the
        2010s, the majority are interactive Web 2.0 websites, allowing visitors to leave online comments, and it is this
        interactivity that distinguishes them from other static websites. In that sense, blogging can be seen as a form
        of social networking service. Indeed, bloggers not only produce content to post on their blogs but also often build
        social relations with their readers and other bloggers. However, there are high-readership blogs which do not
            allow comments.</string>
    <string name="content3">An essay is, generally, a piece of writing that gives the author own argument, but the definition
        is vague, overlapping with those of a letter, a paper, an article, a pamphlet, and a short story. Essays have
        traditionally been sub-classified as formal and informal. Formal essays are characterized by "serious purpose,dignity,
        logical organization, length, whereas the informal essay is characterized by "the personal element
        (self-revelation, individual tastes and experiences, confidential manner), humor, graceful style, rambling structure,
        unconventionality or novelty of theme, etc.
        \n\n
        Essays are commonly used as literary criticism, political manifestos, learned arguments, observations of daily life,
        recollections, and reflections of the author. Almost all modern essays are written in prose, but works in verse have
        been dubbed essays (e.g., Alexander Pope An Essay on Criticism and An Essay on Man). While brevity usually defines
        an essay, voluminous works like John Locke An Essay Concerning Human Understanding and Thomas Malthus An Essay on
        the Principle of Population are counterexamples.
        </string>
</resources>